gosection8.com 2018-12-12

# GoSection8.com - Section 8 Rental Housing & Apartments Listing Service for Landlords & Tenants

This website (“Website”) is operated by Affordable Housing Network, LLC (“AHN” or the “Company”).  This privacy policy governs only the collection of information at the Website, and does not govern the collection of information through other means. Because our business will continue to evolve, we reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time.  Upon any change, we will post the revised policy here, and change the Effective Date noted above.  You are encouraged to check this page periodically so that you are aware of any changed.  If we do make changes, we may send to you, and you agree to receive (unless you have opted-out), an email notifying you about the changes.

**Information Collected About You**

We collect personal information about you whenever you voluntarily provide it to us through the Website, such as when you seek tenant data, place an order or register with us. We consider personal information to be information that identifies you personally, such as your name, credit card information, email and mail address, and telephone numbers.   

  We also collect or log non-personal information about you and your use of the Website. This information includes but is not limited to your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address and your domain name. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer by the Internet Service Provider (“ISP”) computer through which you access the Internet, and a domain name is the name of the ISP computer itself through which you access the Internet.

**Use of Cookies**

A “cookie” is a small piece of information placed on your computer that many web sites use to help make web browsing and shopping easier. This information is stored on your computer's hard drive. The Company does not store personal information in your cookie. We use cookies in order to improve your Website experience. If you choose to register with us, your cookie allows us to recognize you when you return to our site and provides you with access to your account information. Your cookie also assists us in keeping track of your shopping cart. If you request to receive emails from AHN, your cookie helps us deliver messages that we think might be of interest to you.

Our customer service agents also use cookies while using the “live help” service on our website to assist with user support requests.

**How Your Information Is Used**

We use the information you provide to respond to fulfill orders, to respond to a request for information or comments, for our governance practices, and/or other services we provide.  We may also contact you regarding problems or questions we have relating to your use of the Website, or notify you of changes to the Privacy Policy, Terms of Use or other policy or terms that affect you and your use of the Website. We also use your personal information to inform you of our other available products or services. We may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer the Website.  Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart.  We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. 

The Company may enter into strategic partnerships with third parties who may be given access to personal information including your name, address, telephone number and e-mail for the purpose of providing you with information regarding products and services that we think will be of interest to you.  Should you not wish to have your information shared with the Company’s strategic partners, you may opt-out by following the guidelines below. 

We also employ third parties to perform functions on our behalf, such as sending communications, analyzing data, and providing marketing and/or customer services assistance. These third parties may have access to user personal information, to the extent that it is required in order to perform their duties. We may also disclose personal information at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to comply with valid legal processes such as a search warrant, subpoena, or court order, or to protect our rights and property or the property or personal safety of another user of the Website or any member of the public.

With non-personal information, we monitor site use and traffic patterns through server log files and cookies to improve our web site design and the products, courses, and services we offer.   
We reserve the right to disclose, share and/or otherwise transfer user information, including without limitation personal information, in connection with a corporate merger, acquisition, consolidation, the sale of substantially all of company assets, or other fundamental corporate change, whatever form it may take.

**To update, correct or delete your user information**

If at any time you would like us to correct or change any of your personal information on file, feel free to fill out our contact form or call us directly at 866-466-7328. Please be sure to include your email address, full name, and password(s) if you have any. We will process your submission in a timely fashion, and usually respond within 2-3 business days.

**Public Forums**

The Website makes online bulletin boards available to its users.  Use of these areas is subject to the User Obligations and other guidelines set forth in the Website Terms of Use.  Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information, and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Your Security**

We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect the security of your online order information. SSL encrypts your order information to avoid the decoding of that information.  We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, feel free to fill out our contact form.

**Links to Other Web Sites and Services**

AHN's Website may contain links to other sites that are not under our control. These web sites have their own policies regarding privacy. You should review those policies before visiting the web sites. The Company has no responsibility for linked web sites and provides these links solely for the convenience and information of our visitors.

**Opting Out**

Users have the option to opt-out of any email marketing related communications at any time simply by filling out our contact form. You also can call 866-466-7328 or write to us at Affordable Housing Network Customer Service, 5000 T-Rex Ave, Suite 150, Boca Raton, Florida 33431, to opt-out of email and/or postal mail marketing communications.

**Collection and Transfer To The United States**

This Website is operated in the United States. If you are located outside United States, please be aware that any information you provide to us will be collected in or transferred to the United States. By using our Website, participating in any of our services and/or providing us with your information, you consent to this transfer. 

**Not Intended For Children**

This site is not intended for children under the age of 13. We will not knowingly collect information from site visitors in this age group. If you suspect we have received personal information from a child under 13, please contact us and we will delete any such information from our records. 

**Other Questions? Feedback?**

Please let us know if there are other questions you have about your Website experience by filling out our contact form or calling us directly at 866-466-7328. Our customer service hours are Monday through Friday 8AM to 5PM Eastern Time.

**Dispute Resolution**

If you feel that AHN is not abiding by its posted privacy, you should contact us by filling out our contact form.  We will investigate and attempt to resolve any complaints and disputes regarding use and disclosure of personal information in accordance with the principles contained in this Privacy Policy. 

Affordable Housing Network, LLC, Attn.: Customer Service, 5000 T-Rex Ave, Suite 150, Boca Raton, Florida 33431.
